

# Janaka Daskon

46/1, Damunupola, Dedunupitiya

janakadaskon.online

janakadaskon@gmail.com

 $\mathbf{C}$ 

github.com/Janakadaskon

( +94713298540

## PERSONAL PROFILE

Highly motivated, self-learning professional with strong team working skills and a diligent work ethic. I excel in collaborative team environments, leveraging my strong interpersonal skills with experience in this field and a keen interest in staying up-to-date with the latest advancements, I am always on the lookout for new challenges to take on and ways to continue growing as a professional.

#### **EDUCATION**

**BSc. Engineering (Hons)** University of Peradeniya 2016 – 2022 | Peradeniya, Sri Lanka

#### **GCE Advanced Level Examination**

Kg/Mw Pinnawala Central College 2015 | Rambukkana Combined Mathematics -A , Chemistry -A , Physics -B Z-score - 1.9332

## TECHNOLOGY STACK

## **TECHNOLOGIES**

- · Firebase, Google Cloud, Vercel, Netlify
- · Bash Scripts
- · Java, JavaEE, Spring Framework
- · React, Angular
- Node JS, NextJS
- · Tailwind, SASS
- HTML 5, CSS3
- MySQL , PostgreSQL
- JavaScript, ECMAScript, Type Scripts ,Emmet

### **SOFTWARE & TOOLS**

- JetBrains Development Environment
- Visual Studio Code
- Git , GitHub
- JavaFx, scenebuilder
- Draw.io
- Microsoft Office Package

#### **OPERATING SYSTEMS**

· Linux, Mac, Windows

## LANGUAGE

- English
- Sinhala

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### Institute of Software Engineering, Panadura, Sri Lanka

Trainee Software Engineer July 2023 - Present

 Smart Point of Sale System for Super Market Java | MySQL| Maven| Lombok | JavaScript| CSS| Java-fx

https://github.com/Janakadaskon/Smart\_POS.git

 Fully Responsive Personal Portfolio Website React | Next JS | HTML5 | Java Script | CSS3 | Tailwind CSS

https://github.com/Janakadaskon/my\_portfolio.git janakadaskon.online

 Fully Responsive Restaurant Website HTML5 | Java Script | CSS3 | React | Node JS

https://github.com/Janakadaskon/Grandpa-s-Kitchen.git

 Google Design Clone HTML5 | Bootstrap | CSS3

https://github.com/Janakadaskon/Google-design-clone

 Color Picker App https://github.com/Janakadaskon/Color Picker.git

## EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Member of the IESL Student chapter, University of Peradeniya (2017-2022)
- Member of the Civil Engineering Student Society, University of Peradeniya (2018-2021)
- Senior School Prefect (2012-2014)
- President of School Science Society (2012-2014)

## REFERENCES

#### Dr. Suneth Namal Karunarathna,

Senior Lecturer,
Department of Computer Engineering,
Faculty of Engineering, University Of Peradeniya
namal@eng.pdn.ac.lk
+9476 832 1333

#### Eng. S.L. Sudesh De Silva,

Senior Software Engineer, OrangeHRM Inc. lahirud@orangehrmlive.com +94713583481